celebrity-gossip.net 2004-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Celebrity Gossip

Celebrity Gossip has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.celebrity-gossip.net.  Celebrity Gossip is the sole owner of the information received from this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

**Contests and Sweepstakes**  
When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation. As a condition of receiving any prize, you will be required to submit an Affidavit of Eligibility, for us to ensure that you are eligible to receive the prize according to the Contest Rules.

**Newsletters & Promotional E-mails**  
We offer free newsletters and promotional e-mails as a service to our customers. We will send you newsletters and e-mails periodically listing current specials and deals. To stop receiving our newsletter, send an e-mail to us at [unsubscribe@celebrity-gossip.net](mailto:unsubscribe@celebrity-gossip.net).

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Children**  
We do not intend to collect personal information from anyone under the age of 14. If you are under 14, you should not enter information on this web site and should ask a parent to do so for you.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  * You can send email to [unsubscribe@celebrity-gossip.net](mailto:unsubscribe@celebrity-gossip.net)

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [privacy@celebrity-gossip.net](mailto:privacy@celebrity-gossip.net)

**Changes to This Online Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time, but will not do so without posting the revised policy on this web site. We encourage you to review this privacy policy whenever you visit our web site to make sure you understand how we use the information we collect.

Our Favorite Celebs: [Aaron Carter](http://www.celebrity-gossip.net/aaron_carter.php) | [Britney Spears](http://www.celebrity-gossip.net/britney-spears.php) | [Brittany Murphy](http://www.celebrity-gossip.net/brittany_murphy.php)  

Hot Gossip | Movies | Music | Television | Reality TV | The Royals | [Home](http://www.celebrity-gossip.net/)
